&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们已经完成了第5行的执行，并且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We have finished executing line 5, and
行刑往回移动。
execution moves back.
现在我们在14号线。
Now we're on line 14.
第14行是如何执行的？
How does line 14 execute?
希望在这一点上你对此更有信心
Hopefully at this point you're feeling a little more confident with this
谈话。
conversation.
那么第14行是如何执行的呢？
So how does line 14 execute?
&gt；&gt；学生：询问全局范围是否-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的
&gt;&gt; Student: Asks the global scope if it- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right so
谁在说话？
who's talking?
它将是虚拟机，JavaScript引擎。
It's gonna be the virtual machine, the JavaScript engine.
他在14号线上发现了什么？
And what did he find on line 14?
14号线上有什么？
What do we have right here on line 14?
&gt；&gt；学生2：来源。
&gt;&gt; Student2: A source.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们有一个来源参考，谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We have a source reference, thank you.
我们有一个大理石的来源参考叫做？
We have a source reference for a marble called?
学生2：问。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：问，所以
&gt;&gt; Student2: Ask. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Ask, so
我们要找谁去查？
who are we gonna look that up with?
我们要说，嘿？
We're gonna say, hey?
&gt；&gt；学生：全局范围。&gt；&gt；学生2：红色。
&gt;&gt; Student: Global scope. &gt;&gt; Student2: Red.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嘿，红色范围，嘿全球范围，谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey red scope, hey global scope, thank you.
我有一个大理石的标识符叫？
I have an identifier of a marble called?
&gt；&gt；类：问。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：问，谢谢，
&gt;&gt; Class: Ask. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Ask, thank you,
你知道一个叫Ask的大理石吗？
do you know about a marble called ask?
全局范围的响应将是？
And the response from the global scope is going to be?
&gt；&gt；班级：是的。
&gt;&gt; Class: Yes.
凯尔·辛普森：这是你的红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's your red marble.
所以现在我们去那个红色的大理石，记忆中的那个位置，然后我们说，嘿，
So now we go to that red marble, that location in memory, and we say, hey,
红色大理石，里面有什么？
red marble, what do you have in it?
他有什么？
And what does he have?
&gt；&gt；学生2：问题，问题。
&gt;&gt; Student2: Question, question.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：函数，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The function, right?
他有这个功能。
He has the function.
绿色的水桶，就是在第8行声明的东西。
The green bucket, the thing that was declared on line 8.
现在我们有了一个函数。
So now we have a function.
在第14行，这个小的左括号执行函数。
And on line 14 that little open close parenthesis executes the function.
现在执行移到第9行。
Now execution moves to line 9.
第9行，没有更多的var。
Line 9, there's no more var.
但是我们现在就要结束了，那么我们如何执行第9行呢？
But we're getting to the end now, so how do we execute line 9?
谈话是怎么开始的？
How's the conversation start?
&gt；&gt；学生：嘿，绿色桶。
&gt;&gt; Student: Hey, green bucket.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嘿，绿色桶。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey, green bucket.
嘿，问的范围。
Hey, scope of ask.
我有一个什么样的推荐人？
I have a what kind of reference?
&gt；&gt；学生2：排序。&gt；&gt；学生：接收。
&gt;&gt; Student2: Sorts. &gt;&gt; Student: A receiving.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是一个目标引用，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This is a target reference, right?
接待员也很好。
Receiving is fine too.
我有一个接收方，或者一个称为？的标识符的目标引用。
I have a receiving, or a target reference for an identifier called?
&gt；&gt；学生2：问题。
&gt;&gt; Student2: Question.
&gt；&gt；类：问题。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：提出问题，
&gt;&gt; Class: Question. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Called question,
就在9号线。
right there on line 9.
所以我有这个大理石，听说过吗？
So I have this marble, ever heard of it?
那么这个范围的答案是？
And the answer from that scope is going to be?
是啊。&gt；&gt；班级：是的。
Yes. &gt;&gt; Class: Yes.
学生2：这是你的大理石。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是你的果岭
&gt;&gt; Student2: Here's your marble. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here is your green
大理石，好吗？
marble, okay?
所以现在我们有了绿色的大理石，我们正在分配给它。
So now we have the green marble and we are assigning to it.
所以我们现在不在乎里面有什么
So we don't care what's in it right now.
我们去取右边的值，
We go and get the value from the right-hand side,
我们分配到内存的那个位置，第9行就完成了。
we assign into that location of memory and line 9 is finished.
现在，第10行。
Now, line 10.
我们记得控制台是怎么工作的，对吧？
We remember how the console works, right?
所以Console不会在那里找到它，它会转到全局范围，找到它，
So console doesn't find it there, it goes to the global scope, finds it,
查找名为log的方法。
finds a method called log.
但是在它可以执行log之前，
But before it can execute log,
它必须弄清楚传递给它的是什么，对吗？
it's gotta figure out what's being passed to it, right?
你可以在第10行看到，我们正在向它传递一些东西。
You see there on line 10, that we're passing something into it.
我们路过的是什么？
And what are we passing?
这是对另一颗大理石的引用。
It's a reference to another marble.
所以我们得查一下。
So we gotta look that up.
那么这个查找是如何工作的呢？
So how does that look up work?
&gt；&gt；类：[串音]绿色桶。
&gt;&gt; Class: [CROSSTALK] the green bucket.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嘿，绿色桶，嘿，问的范围，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey, green bucket, hey, scope of ask,
我有一个什么样的推荐人？
I have a what kind of reference?
&gt；&gt；类：源。
&gt;&gt; Class: Source.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：来源参考，谢谢，是什么？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Source reference, thank you, for?
&gt；&gt；类：问题。
&gt;&gt; Class: Question.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：问题，听说过吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Question, ever heard of it?
答案是？
And the answer is?
&gt；&gt；班级：是的。
&gt;&gt; Class: Yes.
凯尔·辛普森：这是你的绿色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's your green marble.
现在，因为我们没有分配给它，
And now, because we're not assigning to it,
现在我们想要它当前的值。
now we want the value that's currently in it.
所以我们去记忆的那个区域。
So we go to that area of memory.
我们取出值，恰好是字符串，为什么在这种情况下？
We pull the value out, which happens to be the string, Why in this case?
并将该参数分配给
And that argument is assigned to the parameter that
正在接收console.log，好吗？
console.log is receiving, okay?
所以争论，我们传递的东西，
So arguments, the things that we pass in,
分配给接收它们的参数。
get assigned to the parameters that receive them.
你可以考虑一个参数，比如我有函数ask()和
You can think about a parameter, like if I had function ask() and
它取了一个参数，这个参数是什么样的参考？
it took a parameter, the parameter is what kind of reference?
&gt；&gt；学生：它就像一个变量名。
&gt;&gt; Student: It's like a variable name.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，但它是一种什么样的参考？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is, but what kind of reference is it?
是那个位置。
It's that position.
&gt；&gt；类：目标。
&gt;&gt; Class: Target.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是一个目标。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's a target.
这是一个目标。如果参数中有变量
It's a target. And if you have a variable in an argument
像第10行那样的位置，那是什么样的参考呢？
position like in line 10, what kind of reference is that?
&gt；&gt；类：源。
&gt;&gt; Class: Source.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是一个来源。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's a source.
所以有一个JavaScript引擎的处理和执行，
So there's a processing and execution of a JavaScript engine,
调整自己考虑处理的两个阶段。
aligning yourselves to think about two stages of processing.
一个阶段，我们找出所有的范围，所有的水桶，所有的弹珠。
One stage where we figure out all the scopes, all the buckets, all the marbles.
第二阶段，我们使用所有这些信息来执行代码。
And the second stage, where we use all that information to execute the code.
恭喜你，我证明你是编译器工程师。
Congratulations, I certify you as compiler engineers.
您已经编译并运行了一个JavaScript程序。
You have compiled and run a JavaScript program.
&gt；&gt；学生：是的。
&gt;&gt; Student: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；类：[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Class: [APPLAUSE]